<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
    <meta type="array">
        <description>CSH for table tx_wecsermons_resource_types</description>
        <type>CSH</type>
        <csh_table>tx_wecsermons_resource_types</csh_table>
        <fileId>EXT:wec_sermons/csh/locallang_csh_resource_types.xml</fileId>
        <labelContext type="array" />
    </meta>
    <data type="array">
        <languageKey index="default" type="array">
            <label index=".description">Types that are made available in resource records.</label>
            <label index=".details">The Resource Type record is made available for selection in the Resource record. The Resource Type title will be listed in the drop-down selection box of a Resource record, and the Visible Resource Fields affect what properties of a Resource are shown.</label>
            <label index="sys_language_uid.description">The language of this resource type.</label>
            <label index="sys_language_uid.details">This should be the default language unless this resource type represents a translation of another language.</label>
            <label index="title.description">Uniquely identifies this Resource Type</label>
            <label index="title.details">The Title field will be shown in the drop-down list of a Resource record.</label>
            <label index="_title.seeAlso">tx_wecsermons_resources:type</label>
            <label index="marker_name.description">The subpart marker defined in the template file.</label>
            <label index="marker_name.details">Marker name is the TYPO3 tag that is used for the subpart in a template file. The subpart describes how resources of this type are rendered. See the documentation of this extension for details.</label>
            <label index="template_name.description">The subpart marker defined in the template file, that explains how resources of this type are rendered, displayed, in single view.</label>
            <label index="template_name.details">Template name defines the template subpart that will render resources of this type in single view. Single view is defined by the plugin, and renders a single record. Resource single views have their own template, which is defined by this field. See the documentation of this extension for details.</label>
			<label index="description.description">The general description given for this resource type.</label>
			<label index="description.details">The description can be used to briefly describe the resource type.</label>
			<label index="icon.description"></label>
			<label index="icon.details"></label>
			<label index="avail_fields.description"></label>
			<label index="avail_fields.details"></label>
        </languageKey>
    </data>
</T3locallang>